Vedat IPEK

95 Wentwoth St. S. Unit:501 L8N 2Y7 Hamilton,ON

ABOUT ME

I have been a physiotherapist and department manager for about 5 years, and then I have worked as a medical sales representative for 1.5 years. I had a great chance to help tons of people in their journey to improve their physical situations and also manage the physiotherapy department. In 2021, I graduated from the Health, Wellness and Fitness program at Mohawk College.

I recently have completed B2B Tech SalesCamp conducted by Palette Skills after college.

I am always eager to learn new things that lead me to get out of my comfort zone.

As a self-motivated, self-disciplined, and detailoriented person, I am looking forward to opportunities that take me and my career to the next level.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Mohawk College – Hamilton, ON Health, Wellness, and Fitness 2019-2021

Dokuz Eylül University – Izmir, TURKEY Physical Therapy and Rehabilitation 2006-2012

CERTIFICATION

B2B Tech SalesCamp Palette Skills 02/2022

Standart First Aid & CPR/AED Level C Canadian Red Cross Expiry Date: 10/12/2023

Ares Tape / Therapeutic Kinesiology
Tape
Erkan ALP, PT, MSc 2014 Istanbul, TURKEY

289 952 7782 vedatipek87@hotmail.com <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/vedat-ipek-437411a7/</u>

WORK HISTORY

Order Picker

Superior Radiant Products Stoney Creek, ON November 2021- April 2022 Full-time job after college

Food Machine Operator

Olivieri Foods Limited Hamilton, ON February 2021 – July 2021 Part-time job during studying

Medical Sales Representative & Physiotherapy Consultant Senyuzler Special Education and Rehabilitation Center Izmir, Turkey March 2017 – Oct 2018 Leading for the products that patients need to use Teaching patients how to use, when to use Providing patients with technical support

Physiotherapist & Administrative Manager

Cagnur Special Education and Rehabilitation Center Izmir, Turkey June 2012 – Feb 2017 Creating and implementing the personalized physiotherapy programs

Interviewing with the patients to plan their programs Supervising the physiotherapy department Coordinating the schedules of the patients/therapists Recording-analyzing the medical reports of the patients

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- · Sales & Marketing
- Microsoft Office
- Math skills
- · Administrative management
- Detail-oriented
- · Self-motivated, self-disciplined
- Coachable person